威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们找到了我们的公主。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We have our printHello.
我们有自己的区域。
We have our blockFor1Sec.
我们将这个命名为 setTimeout。
We're going to call this setTimeout.
对 JavaScript 有兴趣吗，凯拉？
Is setTimeout doing anything in
JavaScript of interest, Kayla?
屏幕外的女性: 没有。
&gt;&gt; off screen female: No.
不，在 JavaScript 中什么都没有。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No,
nothing in JavaScript.
然后我们会叫出1秒区。
Then we're gonna call out blockFor1Sec.
然后我们来看看,
And then we're gonna, let's see,
也许下次我们不会叫出1秒区了。
well maybe we're not gonna call
out blockFor1Sec for next.
谁知道呢，我们拭目以待。
Who knows, we shall see.
这就是我们的全球记忆。
So, there's our global memory.
一号线凯拉有什么事吗？
Line one, Kayla, what are we up to?
我们正在定义 printHello 函数。
&gt;&gt; off screen female: We're
defining the printHello function.
非常好，我们正在定义 printHello 函数。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice,
we're defining the printHello function.
好极了，下一句是杰夫。
Excellent, next line over to Jeff.
关闭屏幕男: 我们定义一个函数，blockfor1秒。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: We define a function,
blockFor1Second.
威尔 · 森坦斯: blockFor1Sec，没错，就是这个。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: blockFor1Sec,
exactly, there it is.
我们不知道怎么回事，我是说，我们知道怎么回事。
We don't know how it's, I mean,
we know how it's gonna work.
我们不会写出代码但如果我们运行它,
We're not writing its code out,
but if we ran it,
你会运行某种 for 循环，或者类似的东西。
you would run some sort of for
loop, or something like that.
绝对不是定时器，只是要说清楚。
Definitely not a timer, just be clear.
这是一个很容易掉进去的陷阱。
It's an easy trap to fall into.
现在，事情变得有趣了。
Now, things get interesting.
现在，我们开始我们的第一个 facade 函数
Now, we hit our first facade function for
网页浏览器的一个特性，setTimeout。
a feature of the web browser, setTimeout.
我们会邀请伊森，不，不，不，伊森的台词很棒。
And we're going to invite Ethan, no, no,
no [LAUGH] Ethan's line was excellent.
我们不会再重蹈覆辙了。
We're not gonna put even
through that again.
这次是0。
printHello, and this time is 0.
我是说，第二次等待。
I mean, the second wait.
好的，我应该从那里把它们给你。
Okay, I should give
them to you from there.
我们对 JavaScript 有什么感兴趣的吗？
setTimeout, do we have anything
in JavaScript of any interest?
不，相反，在一个命令中
No, what instead is in a command to
我们屏幕上的哪一部分
which part of our-
&gt;&gt; off screen male: It's gonna send
给浏览器发信息？
a message to the web browser?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 说得好，它会在浏览器中触发,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nicely put,
it's gonna trigger in the web browser,
计时器的开关，计时器的开关。
the switching on of the timer, of a timer.
它需要什么信息，马克，才能成为一个有效的计时器？
And what information does it need here,
Mark, to be an effective timer?
屏幕外的男性: 实际时间。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: The actual time.
是的，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, right?
0毫秒，还有，伊森？
0 milliseconds, and also, Ethan?
关闭屏幕男: 功能定义 printHello？
&gt;&gt; off screen male: The function
definition printHello?
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，那就是我们要在计时器完成后运行的东西。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, that's what we're
gonna run on the completion of the timer.
很好，非常好。
Perfect, very nice.
这一切大概发生在什么时间？
And this is all happening
at roughly what time?
也许0毫秒或者类似的东西，大概0毫秒，就是这样。
Maybe 0 milliseconds or something like
that, roughly 0 milliseconds, there it is.
现在，我们需要下面的所有东西来成为我们的 Web 浏览器。
Now, we need everything below
here to be our Web Browser.
就是这样,
So there it is,
网页浏览器功能。
Web Browser features.
网页浏览器的功能定时器在网页浏览器。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Web Browser
features Timer in the web browser.
所以我们说我们的功能
So we'd say the feature we're
用的是计时器。
gonna use is the Timer.
打开计时器，将其时间设置为完成0毫秒。
Turn on a timer, set its time to
completion to be 0 milliseconds.
当它完成的时候，再次提醒我们，马特，当它完成的时候。
On its completion, just remind us,
again, Matt, on completion.
我们希望发生什么？
What do we want to have happen?
你想让它运行 printHello。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: You want
it to run the printHello.
完美，运行 printHello 函数。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Perfect,
run the printHello function.
所以我们要把一个参考信息传递到网页浏览器,
So we're going to pass into
the web browser a reference,
一个回到我们想要在 JavaScript 中运行的函数的链接。
a link back to the function
we want to run in JavaScript.
但是现在把它想象成函数，所以只是在 JavaScript 或者
But think of it as being the function is
now, so just be outside of JavaScript or
至少它已经准备好了,
at least it's sitting there ready,
希望在某个时候能在 JavaScript 中运行。
hopefully to be run back inside
JavaScript at some point.
现在提问这次我想请凯拉帮忙。
Now question,
I wanna turn to Kayla on this one.
凯拉是0毫秒,
Kayla, is at 0 milliseconds,
0毫秒计时器完成了吗？
is our 0 millisecond timer complete?
屏幕外的女性: 没有。
&gt;&gt; off screen female: No.
句子: 0分钟计时器在0毫秒，你认为呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 0 minute timer at
0 milliseconds, what do you think?
是这样吗? 威尔 · 森坦斯: 它完成了吗？
Is that kinda,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Is it complete?
它怎么会超过0毫秒呢？
How would it take any
longer than 0 milliseconds?
托德，你没有完成。
Todd, you didn't complete.
好的，我的问题是,
&gt;&gt; off screen male: Okay,
so my question would be,
0毫秒和0毫秒是一样的吗？
is that 0 milliseconds the same
as that 0 milliseconds?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，0毫秒,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, 0 milliseconds,
我们的0毫秒计时器完成了，各位。
our 0 millisecond timer is complete,
people.
好了，干得好。
There you go, good job.
0毫秒，我们的0毫秒计时器就完成了，对吧？
0 milliseconds, our 0 millisecond
timer is definitely complete, right?
我不知道这需要多少毫秒的时间。
I don't know how many more than
milliseconds it would take.
这就像，是的，0毫秒是一个完整的计时器。
It's like, yeah,
0 millisecond is a complete timer.
因为疯狂的是，它就像已经完成了。
Because crazily, it's like done.
已经结束了，就是这样。
It's done, it's all it is.
这是一个0毫秒的计时器。
It's a 0 millisecond timer.
所以我假设 printHello 被抓住了
So I presume printHello gets grabbed and
威尔 · 森塔斯: 打电话给斯塔克。
put on to the,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Call Stack.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们认为人们是怎样的？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What do we think people?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 然而，它是完整的，所以它的时间
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And yet,
it is complete and so it's time for
函数到调用堆栈上。
the function to go onto the Call Stack.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我要确保我的脚是最好的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I'm making
sure I stand on my best foot.
特纳告诉我这是我最好的角度。
Turner told me this is my best angle.
它是完整的，所以我想你得到，民间,
It is complete, so I guess you get, folk,
我们还需要知道另一个谜题。
there's another part to the puzzle
that we need to know about.
我就不拐弯抹角了。
And I'm not gonna beat
around the bush on it.
我现在要说的就是这个。
I'm gonna talk about it right now,
which is this.
它叫做，它是一个队列。
It's called, it's a queue.
当你们谈论这件事的时候，我从几个人那里听到了这个词。
I heard the word said from a few
people when you were talking about it.
这是一个队列，我们怎么称呼这些？
It's a queue of, what do we call these?
我们把传递到其他函数中的 baby 函数叫什么？
What do we call baby functions that
get passed into other functions?
作为输入传递到其他函数的小函数。
Little functions that get passed
as inputs into other functions.
男: 回电。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: Callback.
Will Sentance: Callback，所以它是一个回调队列。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Callback,
so it's a queue of callbacks.
回调队列。
A callback queue.
不要以这种方式混淆它，或者不要将这些回调与那些回调混淆
Do not by the way confuse it, or do not
confuse these callbacks with the ones
我们昨天看到它们运行在高阶函数的内部。
we saw yesterday where they run
inside of the higher order function.
不，不，不，这个是被抓住扔出去的。
No, no, no, this one is grabbed and
thrown right out of.
这只是一个命令。
This is just a command.
没有任何一点是 printHello 运行内部的 setTimeout。
At no point is printHello
run inside of setTimeout.
他们只是抓住这个功能，设置它，然后
They just grabbed that function,
set it and
把计时器放进网页浏览器，就存在这里了。
threw into the timer into the web
browser and it's stored here.
或者至少一个指向它最初定义的地方的链接存储在那里。
Or at least a link to where it was
originally defined is store there.
此刻,
At this moment,
在0毫秒时，printHello 不会直接进入调用堆栈。
at 0 milliseconds, printHello ain't
going on the Call Stack directly.
它必须在这里排队进入回调队列,
It's gonna have to queue itself up
here into the callback queue it goes,
在0毫秒，准备运行。
at 0 milliseconds, ready to run.
这是我们的朋友 printHello
There's our friend printHello, and
它会放在回调队列中，准备运行。
it's gonna sit in the callback
queue ready to run.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 但它仍然准备好了，所以我想现在,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But
it's still ready so I guess now,
当我们完成 setTimeout 的时候，我们会继续,
as we complete the setTimeout,
we're gonna pile on,
加速到我们的下一条线，丹，以1毫秒的速度。
accelerated on to our next line which,
Dan, at 1 millisecond.
屏幕外的男性: 我们要叫做 blockFor1Sec？
&gt;&gt; off screen male: We're
going to call blockFor1Sec?
威尔 · 森特斯: 可是，小王子正坐在那儿等着呢。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But, little
printHello is sitting there waiting.
谁认为丹是对的？
Who thinks Dan's right?
丹说得很对。
Dan is spot on.
我们要打电话给1秒区。
We are gonna call blockFor1Sec.
非常有趣。
Most interesting.
1 / sec.
blockFor1Sec.
全新的执行环境。
Brand new execution context.
我们不会过一遍细节。
We're not gonna sort of
go through its details.
但是，我为它添加了如此多的细节，全新的执行环境。
But, I'm adding so much detail for
it, brand new execution context.
就是这个。
There it is.
然后我们的死刑线就会编织进来。
And our thread of execution
is gonna weave in.
它将进入调用堆栈。
It's going on the call stack.
1 / sec，我们以1毫秒进入它。
blockFor1Sec, we go into
it at 1 millisecond.
里面需要1000毫秒。
It's gonna take 1,000 milliseconds inside.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 现在我们有个问题。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Now
we have the question.
在任何时候，我们是否认为，当我们在 blockFor1Sec 时，它正在做 for 循环,
At any moment, do we think, while we
are in blockFor1Sec, it's doing for loop,
很多很多的重复。
lots and lots of iteration.
在那里的任何时刻,
At any moment there,
我们认为 printHello 可以在调用堆栈上运行吗？
do we think printHello is allowed out of
that queue to be run on the call stack?
并非如此。
It's not.
但是我的天啊，它已经等了0毫秒了。
But my goodness,
it's been waiting for 0 milliseconds.
我们将以1001毫秒的速度从1秒区出来。
We're gonna come out of
blockFor1Sec at 1001 milliseconds.
我们的小 printHello 会说，好的，最后，你完成了你的功能。
And our little printHello is gonna say,
okay, finally, you finish your function.
你把它从调用堆栈上弹出来，我们把它从调用堆栈上弹出来。
You popped it off the call stack,
let's pop it off the call stack.
好吧，我终于可以出去了。
Okay, finally, I'm allowed out.
它一直在那里焦急地等待，非常兴奋，说，“我想出来。”。
And it's been waiting there quite eagerly,
very excited, say, I wanna come out.
我想从队列中走出来进入调用堆栈。
I wanna [LAUGH] be out of
the queue into the call stack.
最后在1001毫秒，我们认为会发生什么？
And finally at 1001 milliseconds,
what do we think happens?
可以出去吗？
Is it allowed out?
男: 是的。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: Yes.
威尔 · 森特斯: 不，它仍然不允许外出。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No,
it's still not allowed out.
(笑声)
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH]
威尔 · 森特斯: 相反,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Instead,
我们可怜的小 printHello 会坐在那里，然后用什么来代替呢，Todd？
our poor little printHello is gonna sit
there and what's gonna run instead, Todd?
先给我登陆。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: The console.log
me first.
威尔 · 森特斯: console.log me first，exactly right。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: console.log me first,
exactly right.
我们的 console.log 我第一。
Our console.log me first.
在那里它进入我们的控制台
There it is into our console will be
记录在1001毫秒。
logged at 1,001 milliseconds.
我先说。
Me first.
完全正确。
Exactly right.
我的天啊。
My goodness.
现在是1002毫秒,
Now at 1002 milliseconds,
你们说出来都很紧张。
you're all nervous to even say it.
在1002毫秒，现在，好的，这是我的声音，我会用 Mile 的 yes 声音。
At 1002 milliseconds, now surely, okay,
that's my voice, I'll do Mile's yes voice.
现在，布雷登，你认为什么才能被允许跑步
Now, Brayden, what do you think
is gonna be allowed to run and
被放在调用堆栈上吗？
be put on the call stack?
屏幕外的男性: printHello。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: printHello.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 《王子》 ，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: printHello,
exactly right.
在1002毫秒，printHello 抓住了
At 1002 milliseconds,
printHello grabbed out
放在调用堆栈上，就是这个,
of the queue, put on the call stack,
and there it is,
printhello 的执行时间为1002毫秒。
printHello is executed
at 1,002 milliseconds.
因此，布雷登，我们在控制台上看到了什么？
Therefore, Brayden,
we see in our console, what?
银幕下的男性: 你好。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: Hello.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 你好，没错。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Hello, exactly.
天啊，又来了。
My god, there we go.
所以乡亲们，你们能不能试着确定。
So folk, can you try and ascertain.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，你能试着弄清楚我们的基本原则是什么吗,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes, can you try and
ascertain what is our fundamental,
这就是我刚学会的一个词的最低点。
that was my low point trying
to use a word I just learned.
我们能否试着弄清楚我们的规则是为了什么
Can we try and
ascertain what was our rule for
当队列中的一个函数
when a function in the queue that's being
通过使用这些外观函数之一抛出，进入网页浏览器。
thrown out by using one of these facade
functions, out into the web browser.
并不是真的在 JavaScript 中做任何事情。
setTimeout ain't really doing
anything in JavaScript.
相反，它只是抓住那个函数，[声音] ，把它扔到这里。
Instead, it's just grabbing that function,
[SOUND], throwing it out here.
是什么规则使得它在排队之后,
What is the rule by which after it's
been sitting in the queue, queued up,
准备运行，通过这种方式它被允许从队列中到调用堆栈上。
ready to run, by which it's allowed
out of that queue onto the call stack.
有人能猜出来吗？
Can anyone take a guess?
大概分为两部分。
There's sort of two parts to it.
是的，说吧，马特。
Yeah, go ahead, Matt.
当当前运行的执行上下文完成时。
&gt;&gt; off screen male: When the execution
context currently running is complete.
威尔 · 森特斯: 绝对是，所以如果你在调用堆栈上有任何东西，就必须离开。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Absolutely, so if you've
got any on the call stack, gotta be gone.
但不仅如此。
But it's more than that.
太严格了。
It's so strict.
是的，凯拉。
Yeah, Kayla.
银幕外的女性: 全球执行环境必须完成。
&gt;&gt; off screen female: The global
execution context has to be done.
Will Sentance: 它实际上是所有的同步代码，所有的常规执行。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's in fact all
synchronous code, all regular execution.
也就是说你有可能正如 Kayla 所说,
Meaning you could have,
which is exactly what Kayla's saying,
你可以有一百万根木头，排成一行。
you could literally have
a million console.logs in a row.
你可以有一个 console.log 的无限 while 循环，并且
You could have an infinite
while loop of console.log, and
队伍永远不会让 printHello 退队。
the queue would never dequeue printHello.
它甚至不会抓取它并将其放到调用堆栈上。
It would never even grab it and
put it on the call stack.
对我来说我承认当我第一次意识到,
And that, to me, I will admit,
when I first realized that,
我得去看看。
I had to go and check that.
我简直不敢相信你真的，真的有一百万块圆木。
I couldn't believe you could literally,
literally have a million console.logs.
而且他们都会在任何事情被排除在队伍之外之前跑掉。
And they would all run before
anything was out of the queue.
这听起来很疯狂，但是
That seems insane, but
它实际上让我们能够确定，我们的代码何时会用完一个队列。
it actually allows us to be certain of
when our code will run out of a queue.
这可能不是我所知道的那个时刻的意义上的确定。
It may not be the certain in
the sense of I know the moment.
但我知道顺序。
But I do know the order.
所有常规代码将首先运行，直到我碰到队列中的任何东西,
All regular code will run first until
I ever touch anything from the queue,
直到我把任何东西从队列中拿出来。
until I ever put anything
out of the queue.
那么，JavaScript 是如何实现的呢？
So, how does JavaScript implement that?
嗯，它有一个小小的特点，非常深刻的特点。
Well, it has a little tiny feature,
very profound feature.
但实际上它只能做一件事,
But really, it just does this one thing,
也就是说在每行代码运行之前我都要检查。
which says I'm gonna check before
every single line of code run.
调用堆栈是空的吗？
Is the call stack empty?
有什么事情在排队吗？
Is there something in the queue?
如果调用堆栈不是空的，如果还有其他全局代码要运行，如果
If the call stack is not empty, if there's
still further global code to run, if
还有更多的全局代码要运行，那么我甚至不会去查看队列。
there's still further global code to run,
then I will not even go look at the queue.
但如果调用堆栈是空的或
But if the call stack's empty or
如果我下到队列，我抓住函数，把它放在调用堆栈上。
if I head down to the queue, I grab
the function, I put it on the call stack.
这个被称为小特征的东西是什么？
And what is that known
as that little feature?
这个小功能可以非常非常快速地检查
That little feature that does the very,
very fast checking
每一行代码运行之前，它都会检查。
every single line before it runs
any line of code, it checks.
调用堆栈上有什么东西吗？
Is there anything on the call stack?
如果有的话，就去做吧。
If there is, just do it.
还有什么东西在全局运行吗，快点。
Is there anything left running global,
do it.
如果都完成了，就去排队。
If it's all finished,
head down to the queue.
这个特性被称为事件，Will Sentance: Loop。
And that feature is known as the Event,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Loop.
而它的工作就是非常简单地不断地快速检查。
And it's job is simply to very
quickly be checking constantly.
调用堆栈是空的吗？
Is the call stack empty?
还有什么要排队的吗？
Is there anything in the queue?
调用堆栈是空的吗？
Is the call stack empty?
还有什么要排队的吗？
Is there anything in the queue?
是否有任何全局代码要运行？
Is there any global code to run?
不，我终于可以下去了。
No, finally I get to go down.
所以我的事件循环始终，是调用堆栈在 blockFor1Sec 为空,
So my event loop throughout goes,
is the call stack empty at blockFor1Sec,
所有人？
everybody?
男: 没有 威尔 · 森特斯: 不,
&gt;&gt; off screen male: No.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No,
我们还是得在1秒内跑完。
we stil got to run in blockFor1Sec.
在1,001毫秒时，还有更多的全局代码需要运行吗？
At 1,001 milliseconds,
is there further global code still to run?
男: 是的 威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，所以
&gt;&gt; off screen male: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, so
事件循环，不，你不能。
the event loop goes, no, you can't.
最后，当所有全局代码运行完毕后，会发生什么？
Finally, when all global code is
finished running, what happens?
它走向队列，它说，是的，我已经准备好进入队列。
It heads down to the queue, it goes, yes,
I'm ready to head down into the queue.
它抓住 printHello，并且它位于调用堆栈上并执行它。
It grabs printHello, and
it sits on the call stack and executes it.
它为我们放上插入语，没有问题，并运行了 printHello。
It puts the parenthesis on for us,
no problem and runs printHello.
对于这个问题，直到他有了6个，就是异步 JavaScript 的整个模型。
And for that until he has six was the
entire model of Asynchronous JavaScript.
因此，让我们对这个概念，我们已经保存了我们的功能
So let's have thumbs on this notion
that we have saved our functions for
1sec 的另一个区块。
another blockFor1Sec.
我们使用 setTimeout 来触发计时器,
We use setTimeout to trigger a timer,
一个相关的 printHello 函数被传递给它。
an associated printHello
function was passed to it.
是的，它说0毫秒，直到这个函数可以运行。
Yes, it said 0 milliseconds until
that function could be run.
但是我们现在知道这到底意味着什么呢？
But what do we now know that really means?
这意味着它是0毫秒，直到这个函数被放入,
It means that it's 0 milliseconds
until that function is put into the,
正如彼得所暗示的，加入了回调队伍。
exactly as Peter's hinting,
into the callback queue.
然后我们所有的全局代码都会继续运行，不管需要多长时间。
And then all our global code's gonna
continue running, however long it takes.
当一切都结束时事件循环就开始了,
And when it's all done,
then the event loop goes,
万岁，调用堆栈完成了。
hooray, the Call Stack is done.
所有的全局沿海地区都完成运行，我们从回调队列中获取并
All global coast finish running, and
we grab from the Callback Queue and
将 printHello 放入调用堆栈。
put printHello in the Call Stack.